[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "dis_ro_ortionately",
    "options": ["V", "Q", "P"],
    "answer": "P"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "co_nterprod_ctive",
    "options": ["A", "U", "Y"],
    "answer": "U"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "uncons_i_u_ionally",
    "options": ["H", "T", "E"],
    "answer": "T"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "_ntercont_nental",
    "options": ["I", "U", "G"],
    "answer": "I"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "misi_terpretatio_",
    "options": ["N", "F", "L"],
    "answer": "N"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "o_ergeneralization",
    "options": ["K", "D", "V"],
    "answer": "V"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "mis_hara_terization",
    "options": ["G", "F", "C"],
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "anti_isestablishment",
    "options": ["K", "D", "R"],
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "di_enfranchi_ement",
    "options": ["K", "S", "W"],
    "answer": "S"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "supercal_frag_l_st_c",
    "options": ["I", "O", "Y"],
    "answer": "I"
  }
]